Guide to the Herbert C. (Herbert Coffin) Jones Papers, 1903-1954
Department of Special Collections
Example of the Division of the correspondnece from even-numbered non-legislative session years into the previous and subsequent odd-numbered legislative session, year's folders: In the 1915 Correspondence folders, the bulk of the letters are dated during the annual legislative session (January-June, 1915).
In addition to these Letters, the 1915 folders contain letters dated in the last months of 1914 (usually July through December), and the letters dated in the first six months of 1916 (January through June). This arrangement of the material is followed from 1913-1925 material.
After 1925, as has been explained, a group of folders identified as After-Session Correspondence, has been created to contain the correspondence of legislative years after the session closes (June thru December of the legislative year), and to contain the correspondence of the even-numbered year which follows a given legislative year. For example, the 1927 After-Session Correspondence folders will contain letters dated from June, 1927 through 1928, up to the opening of the 1929 Legislative Session in January, 1929.
In a few non-legislative session years such as 1926 and 1932, Senator Jones did receive a greater quantity of correspondence on a given topic than in other even-numbered, non-legislative years. Therefore, in this case a group of folders for the Correspondence and Reference Materials for these even-numbered years has been arranged, separate from the usual incorporation of non-legislative years (correspondence in the folders for legislative years.
Further Notes about the filing of the Correspondence:
Enclosures (clippings, other letters, etc.) in letters sent to Senator Jones have been kept, in most cases, with the letter by the use of a folded yellow sheet. If the enclosures mentioned in certain letters to and from Mr. Jones are not with the letter, refer to the Reference File (1913-1925 material) of the year in which the letter was written, checking under the initial letter and/or title of the subject in question. Or the yellow sheet with a letter will where the original enclosure may be found. Example: If an enclosure on Education is mentioned in a letter to Senator Jones, and this enclosure is not attached to the letter, see the Reference File for the year, under E.
As stated earlier, the material in the collection is filed first chronoligically. However, when material would seem to be more valuabe or meaningful if kept together in one folder rather than distributed in separate folders within various years, this material over different years (such as Consolidation, 1927-1934) is kept together in one folder, filed with folders in the latter year (1934). The cases in which material is kept together although it ranges over a period of years, are few; chronological organization of material has been maintained unless there were good reasons for exception.
Letters which are not dated at all, or are of uncertain dates, are kept with the correspondence of the year with which they were originally received; for filing they are placed at the front of a given folder (for example: with A if the correspondents name begins with this letter--in the 1918-1925 material; or according to the initial letter of the subject of the letter in the 1925-1954 material). Although a letter be of uncertain date, if it can be ascertained from other letters, approximately what month it was written in, the letter is placed at the end of a group of other letters in a given month.
Reference Material:
Bills. A list of the bills introduced by Senator Jones in a given legislative session are arranged in folder labeled B in the Reference folders, from 1918-1925. For Bills after 1925, 1925-1954, Bills are filed in a separate folder labeled Bills in sectio B of the group of folders known as Legislative Correspondence, filed by Subject Matter.
Container List
- PRE-ELECTION MATERIAL
  - Political campaign: platform of the Progressive party. First National Convention - Roosevelt and Johnson, 1913. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence pertaining to the election of Jones to state senate, 2 Jan. 1913. (Box 1, Folder 2a)
  - H.C. Jones' election to state senate: miscellaneous material, 1913. (Box 1, Folder 2b)
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1912-1913.
  (Chronological within folders)
  - A (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - B (Nov. 1912 - March 1913) (Box 1, Folder 4a)
  - B (April 1913 - Dec. 1913) (Box 1, Folder 4b)
  - C (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - D (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - E (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - F (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - G (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - H (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - I (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - J (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - K (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 15M (January through March 31, 1913) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - M (April 1, 1918 to April 11, 1914) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - N (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - O (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - PQ (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - R (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - T (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - UV (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - W (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - XYZ (Box 3, Folder 25)
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1913.
  - Anti-Alien Land Bill (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bids for Building, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Billboards, Blue Sky Law, Boiler Inspection (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Cement Bill (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Cemetery Removal
  - Civil Service
  - Combinations
  - Conservation
  - County Government Bill
  - Crime
  - Dredges (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Dry Zone
  - Education (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Eight Hour law
  - Eugenics
  - Elections
  - Embalmer's Bill
  - Ferries (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Fish and Game
  - Forestry
  - Fraternities
  - Public Health and Quarantine Committee (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Injunction (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Insurance
  - Irrigation
  - Japanese Immigration (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Judiciary and Legal Reform
  - Labels, Manufacturer's name on (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Labor
  - Legislative Reference Bureau
  - Liquor
  - Mechanic's Lien Law (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Medical (see also: Public Health and Quarantine folder) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous material, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Peace Societies (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Pension for Teachers
  - Pipe Line Bill
  - Port San Jose
  - Progressives
  - Public Ownership (Government Ownership), 1913-1914
  - Roads and Highways (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Senate (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Social Evil
  - Socialism
  - State Fair
  - Sunday Law
  - Taxation (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Torrens Land Act
  - Tuberculosis
  - Vaccination (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Vice
  - Viticultural Industry
  - Workmen's Compensation
- RECREATIONAL ENQUIRY COMMITTEE, 1913-1916
  - Correspondence: A thru Q (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence: R (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence: S-Z (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous material (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - H.C. Jones' Political Campaign and Election, 1914:Correspondence, A through B (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - H-R Correspondence, A through B (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - H.L. Jones' Political Campaign and Election, 1914:Correspondence S through Z (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - H.L. Jones' Political Campaign and Election, 1914:Miscellaneous Material (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Other Political Campaigning, 1914-1916:Correspondence A-Z (for;Political Campaigning, 1914,see also folders no. 1955, 1056, File Drawer no. 17 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1915,(contains letters pertaining to Leg. Sess. 1915 (- 1917) (1914 -),divided by letter, chrono within by writer, receiver, organiz., or subject. Some grouped regardless to chrono same correspondent
  - A (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - B - January 1914 - March 1915 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - B - April 1915 - 1916 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - C - January 1915 - March 1915 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - C - April 1915 - 1916 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - D (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - E-F (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - G (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - H (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - I (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - J (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - K (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - L (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - M - January 1914 - March 1915 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - April 1915 - 1916 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - N (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - O (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - P (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Q (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - R (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - S - January 1914 - February 1915 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - March 1915 - 1916 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - T (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - UV (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - W-Z (Box 9, Folder 78)
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1915
  - Acknowledgement (Act to amend the Civil Code) (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Agnew State Hospital. Director, Leonard Stocking
  - Agriculture, Department of
  - Alien Teachers
  - Apprentices
  - Architects
  - Automobiles
  - Bible in Public Schools (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Bills introduced by Senator Jones, 1915Session (not passed)
  - Bird and Arbor Conservation
  - Blindness
  - Blue Sky Law
  - Bohnett, Assemblyman, Bills introduced by, 1915Session
  - Capital Punishment (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Chattel Mortgages
  - Cement Bill
  - Cemetaries
  - Charities and Corrections, State Board of
  - Colleges
  - Compensation Insurance
  - Corporation Bills
  - County Government
  - District Attorneys (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Education
  - Elections Equalization, State Board of
  - Farmer's News: Direct Legislation
  - Fire Department: Two Platoon Issue
  - Fish and Game
  - Forest fire legislation
  - Fraudulent Representation
  - Gambling (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Grant, Senator E.E.: Recall Election
  - Imperial Valley Road
  - India Basin (SB 1209)
  - Injunctions
  - Insurance
  - Irrigation Districts
  - Japanese (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Jitneys Automobile Transportation
  - Judges, appointment of
  - Judiciary Committee: Leases, legal reform, miscellaneous
  - Jury System
  - Juvenile Court
  - Labor (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Lick Observatory
  - Loan Sharks
  - Liquor
  - Legislature, 1915:Senate Daily Journal
    Inaugural Ceremonies Constitutional restrictions on Legislative Power
  - Market Bill (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Medical
  - Miscellaneous, 1915
  - Municipalities, Bills of interest to
  - Music, Teaching of (AB543)
  - Normal Schools (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Non-Partisanship, 1914-1915:Newspaper Clippings, letters, etc.
  - Non-Partisanship Bill, Johnson Administration, aimed at political and judicial reform, breaking control of machine and securing government in the hands of the people.
  - Oil
  - One Day of Rest in Seven Law: Sunday Closing Law
  - Park Commission (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Pension, Widow's Press Association
  - Plumbing
  - Panama - Pacific Exposition
  - Railroads
  - Redwood Park Trip
  - Roads and highways (John Muir Trail)
  - Senate (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Schools (see: Education, teachers)
  - Sheriffs
  - Short Ballot
  - Socialism
  - Taxation (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Teachers (see also: Education, Schools)
  - Tuberculosis
  - University of California, Berkeley (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Usury
  - Vaccination
  - Water Supply
  - Safety W indow Legislation
  - Women's organizations
  - Workmen's Compensation Insurance and Safety Act
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 92)
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1917
  - A (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - B - January 1916 - February 1917 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - B - March 1917 - 1918(Box a) (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - C - January 1916 - March 1917 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - C - April 1917 - 1918 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - DEF (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - G (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - H (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - IJK (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - L (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - M - January 1916 - March 1917 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - M - April 1917 - 1918(Box 12), (*yellow) (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - NO (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - P (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - QR (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - S (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - TUV (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - W (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - XYZ (Box 12, Folder 111)
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1917
  - Agnews (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Almshouse
  - Apprentices
  - Arbitration
  - Army
  - Bar Association (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Big Basin
  - Birds
  - Building and Loan Association
  - Bills introduced by Senator Jones, 1917Legislature
  - Capital (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Capital Punishment
  - Chamber of Commerce
  - Child Labor
  - Christian Science
  - Churches
  - Community Charters, Community Property
  - County Clerks, County Assessors
  - Cooperatives
  - Death Penalty (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Deciduous Fruit Experiment Station
  - Drinking Cup Law
  - Dumbarton Bridge
  - Education (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Eight hour law
  - Employment
  - Expert Testimony
  - Farm labor (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Farmers' Union
  - Fish and Game law
  - Grand Jury
  - Grape Growing Industry
  - Handbook, Legislative for 1917
  - Happy Valley Irrigation district
  - Health Insurance
  - Identification of criminals (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Indeterminate Sentence, Association for
  - Indians
  - Injunctions
  - Insurance
  - Jail (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Jitneys
  - Jury System
  - Justices of the Peace
  - Jones and Benson
  - Johnson, Mira - Outlook magazine
  - Labor (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Lane Settlement Act
  - Legal Reform
  - Legislation, 1917:Miscellaneous
  - Liquor
  - Market Act (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Mediation
  - Medical
  - Military Training in Schools
  - Miscellaneous, 1917
  - Morons
  - Mother's pension
  - Military Training, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - Normal School (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1917
  - Oakland (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Pamphlets
  - Pensions for Police
  - Physical Training in Schools
  - Political
  - Printing, Office, State
  - Prison
  - Probation
  - Prohibition
  - Public Defenders
  - Real Estate
  - Reclamation
  - Registration for Draft
  - Reclamation: Correspondence. January 1914 - March 1917. (Box 14, Folder 125)
    Senator Jones, Chairman of Senate Committee on Drainage, Swamp and Overflow Lands. Reorganization of California State Reclamation Board. Jones sought to replace current Board by Board of three. His committee studied the Reclamation Board Act.
  - April 1917 - June 1917 (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Reclamation: Clippings, Amendments, etc. (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Reclamation: Reports, Maps, Bills, Speeches, Pamphlets, etc. (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Reclamation: Reports, Maps, Bills, Speeches, Pamphlets, etc., (continued) (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Schools (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - Seeds
  - Senate
  - Short Ballot
  - Social Insurance (see: Health Insurance)
  - Sunday Closing Law
  - Sutter Basin
  - Salon Closing Campaign (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - San Pedro Harbor
  - Taxes
  - Teachers' Pension
  - Textbooks
  - Tioga Road
  - Torrens T-Hes
  - Trading Stamps
  - Trappers
  - Trusts
  - Tulare Lake District
  - Usury, Visual Education (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Vivisection
  - Vocational Education
  - Vivisection (Bill No. 798) (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Water (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Women's Bills
  - Workmen's Compensation Act
  - Y.M.C.A.
  - Folders 135 and 136 contain material pertaining to 1918 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - A-K (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - L-Z (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - POLITICAL CAMPAIGNING IN PREPARATION FOR THE COMING ELECTIONS. The bulk of the material is correspondence filed under the first letter of the sendor or receiver and is chronological within the letter divisions. The remainder of the material consists of election-folders, photos, pamphlets, etc., which are filed alphabetically by the subject or candaidate to which they refer. (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - 1918Reference Material: (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - Child Labor
    - Dry Amendment/Dry Candidates
    - Health Insurance
    - Gov. Johnson
    - Statutes, compiled
    - War Work Campaign
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1919
  - A (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - B (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - 1918 - March 1919 (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - April 1919 - 1920 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - D (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - E (Box 16, Folder 143)
  - F (Box 16, Folder 144)
  - G (Box 16, Folder 145)
  - H (Box 16, Folder 146)
  - I (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - J (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - K (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - L (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - M (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - N (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - O (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - P (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - R (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - 1918 - February 1919 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - S: March 1919 - 1920 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - T (Box 18, Folder 158)
  - UV (Box 18, Folder 159)
  - W (Box 18, Folder 160)
  - XYZ (Box 18, Folder 161)
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1919
  - Agriculture Bills (Box 18, Folder 162)
  - American Committee for Armenian and Syrian Relief
  - Americanism
  - Apples, standardization of
  - Automobiles, stealing
  - Appropriation
  - Banks (Box 18, Folder 163)
  - Bar Association
  - Bee Keepers
  - Bennet, Bills supported by
  - Berry Growers
  - Big Basin Project
  - Bills endorsed by teachers
  - Building and Loan
  - Bills introduced by Senator Jones, Legislative Session, 1919.Note on filing of Bills: Bills may be filed several ways--under B of Reference Material for a given legislative year; other copies of Bills may be filled according to the subject or topic about which they are concerned; they may be filed under title of the committee (s) to which they are referred by legislature. Usually, the copies of Bills under B of Reference Material file are those which were introduced into legislature by Senator Jones. (Box 18, Folder 164)
  - Capital Punishment (Box 18, Folder 165)
  - Carnahan, H.B.
  - Cemetery Protection
  - Chamber of Commerce, San Francisco
  - Child aid
  - Child Hygiene Bureau
  - Child Labor Law
  - Clear Lake
  - Coca Cola
  - Commercial Federation
  - Community Property
  - Congressional Record
  - Corporations
  - County Gov't.
  - Dairy Laws (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - Deaf and Blind, School for
  - Delinquent Women, State Home for
  - Education (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - Employment Agencies
  - Experiment Station for Decidious Fruit
  - Expert Testimony
  - Education. Education Committee: Correspondence, February 1919 - April 1919 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - Education. Education Committee: Correspondence Bills, Amendments, etc. (Box 19, Folder 169)
  - Farmers (Box 19, Folder 170)
  - Feed Standards
  - Fees, official
  - Finances
  - Fish and Game
  - Fire Boats
  - Forestry
  - Grand Jury (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - German, teaching of in California Schools
  - Government control of Railroads
  - Harbor, San Francisco (see also under S)
  - Hay
  - Health Insurance
  - Hill, Andrew
  - Historian--Mighels
  - Homesteads
  - Hunter's Point Project
  - Industrial Accident Commission
  - Initiative
  - Injunction
  - Insurance
  - Irrigation
  - I.W.W.
  - Japanese: immigration, land ownership, picture brides (Box 19, Folder 172)
  - Judges' Salaries, volume of business
  - Labor
  - League of Nations
  - Legal Reform
  - Market Act (Box 19, Folder 173)
  - Market Director
  - Meadow Larks
  - Medical Practice Act
  - Military Training in Schools/Militarism
  - Milk Legislation
  - Money Case
  - Motor Vehicles, lights
  - Movies
  - Miscellaneous, 1919
  - Nurses (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - Paint
  - Peace
  - Pension
  - Photographs
  - Pacheco Rancho
  - Presentation
  - Primary Laws
  - Prohibition
  - Probate procedure
  - Psychopathic hospital, state
  - Public Defenders
  - Railroad-postwar readjustment (Box 19, Folder 175)
  - Real Estate
  - Reclamation
  - Reconstruction, postwar
  - Records
  - Red Cross
  - Redwoods League
  - Regulation
  - Reorganization
  - Republicans
  - Roads
  - San Francisco Harbor (Box 19, Folder 176)
  - Santa Clara Boundary
  - Scenic
  - Schools
  - Shearer contest
  - Short Ballot
  - Sloane, W.A., for Judge
  - Social Health Insurance
  - Sunday Closing Law
  - Surety Companies
  - Tidelands (Box 20, Folder 177)
  - Trading Stamps
  - Tuberculosis
  - Universities
  - Venereal Disease
  - Vivisection
  - War Gardens (Box 20, Folder 178)
  - War Risk Insurance
  - Whittier School
  - Wills, inheritance
  - Women's Suffrage
  - Workmen's Compensation
  - Working Reserve, U.S. Boys'
- EDUCATIONAL INVESTIGATING COMMITTEE, 1919
  - Correspondence, A-B (Box 20, Folder 179)
  - Correspondence, C (Box 20, Folder 180)
  - Correspondence, D-H (Box 20, Folder 181)
  - Correspondence, I-M (Box 20, Folder 182)
  - Correspondence, N-T (Box 20, Folder 183)
  - Correspondence, U-Z (Box 20, Folder 184)
  - Reference Materials (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Requests for the Committee's Report, January 18, 1921 through November 3, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Report of the special committee on Education (Box 21, Folder 187)
- INTERSESSION, 1920
  - Correspondence. Filed by Subject Matter: (Box 21, Folder 188)
    - Agriculture
    - Committee of 48 for political, economic, and social reform
    - Constitutional Convention
    - Federal Aid
    - Federal Income Tax
    - Health
    - Herbert Hoover, Near East Relief
    - Japanese
    - Members Forum
    - State University
  - Miscellaneous Materials: Leaflets, Commercial advertisements, publicity, letters, etc. (Box 21, Folder 189)
  - Reference Material. Field by Subject Matter: (Box 21, Folder 190)
    - Commercial Arbitration
    - Consolidation of High School Districts
    - Cox, James M. for President
    - Forestry
    - Harding's Liquor Record-California
    - Johnson Campaign for President
    - Maine Centennial
    - Petroleum Products
    - Case of Charlotte Anita Whitney (Michborn)
    - The California Liberator
- LEGISLATIVE CORRESPONDENCE, 1921,filed by name of correspondent
  - A (Box 22, Folder 191)
  - B, 1920 - February 1921 (Box 22, Folder 192)
  - B, March 1921 - December 1921 (Box 22, Folder 193)
  - C (Box 22, Folder 194)
  - D (Box 22, Folder 195)
  - E (Box 22, Folder 196)
  - F (Box 22, Folder 197)
  - G (Box 22, Folder 198)
  - H (Box 23, Folder 199)
  - I (Box 23, Folder 200)
  - J (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - K (Box 23, Folder 202)
  - L (Box 23, Folder 203)
  - M (Box 23, Folder 204)
  - N (Box 23, Folder 205)
  - O (Box 23, Folder 206)
  - PQ (Box 23, Folder 207)
  - R (Box 23, Folder 208)
  - 1920 - March 1921 (Box 24, Folder 209)
  - S, April 1921 - 1922 (Box 24, Folder 210)
  - T (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - UV (Box 24, Folder 212)
  - UV (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - W, 1920 - March 1924 (Box 24, Folder 214)
  - XYZ, April 1921 - 1922 (Box 24, Folder 215)
- REFERENCE MATERIAL, 1921
  - Advisory Boards (Box 24, Folder 216)
  - Agriculture
  - Arbitration
  - Autos
  - Berry Baskets (Box 24, Folder 217)
  - Better America Federation
  - Big Basin
  - Building and Loan
  - Budget, 1921
  - Capital Punishment (Box 25, Folder 218)
  - Catholics
  - Cattlemen's Association
  - Cemetery Removal
  - Chamber of Commerce
  - Child Labor
  - Chiropractors
  - Collection Agencies
  - Commonwealth Club
  - Community Property
  - Comptroller
  - Counties
  - County Government
  - Coyotes
  - Creditors
  - Crime
  - County Government, 1921(AB 199, Wright Bill) to amend the Political Code in regard to salaries, fees of officers of counties of the fourth class.
  - Dairy Measures (Box 25, Folder 219)
  - Deciduous Fruit
  - Education
  - Eight Hour Law
  - Expert Witnesses
  - Flood Control
  - Foreign Trade
  - Forestry
  - Gasoline
  - Grape Growers' Organization
  - Handbook, Legislature, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 220)
  - Harbor, San Francisco
  - Harris Bill
  - Health
  - High Schools
  - Highways
  - Horticulture
  - Hydro-Electricity
  - Indemnity Certificates (Box 25, Folder 221)
  - Indeterminate Sentence
  - Industrial Accident Commission
  - Initiative
  - Insurance
  - Irrigation
  - Japanese
  - Jews
  - Judges
  - Labor (Box 25, Folder 222)
  - Lake County
  - Land Settlement
  - Law
  - Legislature
  - Manufacturers (Box 25, Folder 223)
  - Marketing Price
  - Marshall Plan
  - Medical
  - Military Training
  - Miscellaneous
  - Motion Pictures
  - Motor Vehicles
  - National Guard (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - Normal Schools
  - Normal Schools vs. Board of Control, 1920-1921
  - Nurses
  - Oleomargarine (Box 26, Folder 225)
  - Osteopaths
  - Power Monopoly
  - Practical Psychology
  - Primary, Direct
  - Prison